Yeah!
In case you just got here, I'm Spider-Man.
And I'm in a race against the clock.
So much to be responsible for,
so little time.
Like weird energy readings
coming from a lab.
Dr. Octopus abandoned before
he went tentacles-up.
But a good leader like me knows
to bring good backup.
Spider, we got company here.
Engaging at the east entry.
Ava Ayala. White Tiger.
Cat-like speed and reflexes.
She's on this.
Power Man,
Iron Fist:
Tiger's down.
Any visual on an adversary?
Yeah. I can't believe it,
but he's alive and moving right for us.
Or is it we who move for him?
Perspective defines reality.
Luke Cage, the super strong Power Man.
And Danny Rand, Iron Fist.
He of chi-powered fist and
haiku shout outs.
They're on this.
Nova, light us up, now!
You don't have to yell in my earpiece,
bug breath.
Jeez.
Sam Alexander. Nova.
Loudmouth with a mega helmet.
He's a flier, a fighter,
and a great big flashlight.
Whoa! Doc Ock, alive?
Reports of my demise were
greatly exaggerated.
This would be really bad
if I wasn't rocking the latest
SHIELD technology.
Now, I'm on this.
You shouldn't have followed me.
I didn't, but I'm glad I found you.
No web fluid? Ah! Yikes!
This is SHIELD. We have you surrounded.
No! Not now!
Nice to see you're keeping
up on your training.
Training?
M-Maybe you didn't notice, Fury,
but my web-shooter's jammed
and Ock got away.
P.S., did you guys even
know he was still alive?
We heard rumors. But at least he
didn't leave with his prize.
Have to give credit where it's due,
Spider-Man.
Your team has been on point lately.
The SHIELD Helicarrier may not be
back up and operational yet,
but you're doing us proud.
I couldn't agree more, Agent Coulson.
Securing Ock's experimental DNA compounds?
Incredible work.
Want to stay and lend me a hand testing
these samples, Spider-Man?
Do I? You bet, Dr. Conners!
Oh, sorry.
Ow! Come on! Stop that! We got to jet.
Teenagers.
Assume position Alpha Three! Hurry!
- We must hurry. Proceed with haste.
- Coming through. Coming through.
Come on! Hurry! We're running out of time.
Hey! Ow!
Come on, come on, come on, come on! Time!
I'm home!
Oh! Hi, Aunt May.
Hey, Ms. Parker.
Hey, guys! What's up?
Any excitement today?
Who has time for excitement?
Welcome to casa de Parker.
After the Helicarrier went kablooey,
my team moved in with me.
I always wondered what a bigger family
would be like and now I know.
Hey! Come on! Ow!
It's been fun,
but it's also taking
a lot of getting used to.
Can I get on the computer, Ava?
I'll be off in just a sec.
I knew that was coming.
Everybody has their own way of adjusting.
I'm just going with the flow
and looking for a place to work
on my broke-down web-shooters.
Ah!
Sorry, Danny.
Luke?
Again?
Takes a routine to look this good.
These days, the basement is the only place
I can be alone.
Small price to pay for family, I guess.
Come on, Aunt May! No pain no gain!
Who kicks butt?
I do!
And cue my exit music. Uh-oh.
Want to stay and lend me
a hand testing these samples,
Spider-Man?
A high-tech lab plus a super
scientist mentor?
That equals the best idea
I ever almost forgot.
No web slinging would be a problem
for an average spider-man,
but an ultimate spidey just says,
"Hello, SHIELD-issued spidey cycle."
Goodbye, gridlock.
Hello, solitude.
Ah. See?
There's your clogging problem.
The intake canister's cracked.
Causing the web fluid to leak. Huh.
You're a lifesaver, Doc.
Me?
No, no, no. That's your job.
I'm just your friendly neighborhood
one-armed scientist.
From the day I first joined SHIELD,
Doc Connors was a hundred percent
cool peeps.
A fellow science geek,
and if I'm being completely honest,
a real mentor for me.
I still feel responsible
for him losing his arm.
There. Good as new.
Uh, better. Tap twice.
Flash webs?
Cool!
Simple upgrade.
Us brains have to stick together, right?
Uh, speaking of which,
I want you to see what Octavius was after.
I think you'll find this particularly
interesting considering your power set.
Whoa! Is this animal DNA?
Do you see what he was getting at?
He wanted to open an evil petting zoo?
I believe Otto was inspired by you
to try and create a group
of people powered
by specific DNA sequences.
Ah. The old "Build an animal army
world domination" gag.
I'm glad we put the kibosh on that.
But place this technology in the hands
of a scientist who isn't a madman and
then what do you get?
He's not thinking what
I think he's thinking.
Is he?
I think these animal compounds could
regenerate a damaged human body.
I know it sounds far-fetched, but,
well, look at how you turned out.
I got lucky.
But look at Venom or-or Goblin
if you want the usual results of Ock's
genetic guesswork.
Of course.
You-You're right.
I shouldn't rush into anything.
Hey,
that doesn't mean we can't dig
deep into his notes.
Okay. Have to be super careful.
Don't want to trip any of Ock's
nutso security.
Just leave that to me.
Welcome, intruder.
You want my tech?
Have at it.
Hey, what is that?
What's going on?
Wilcox, call for backup.
That might be my fault.
The sample vials!
Oh!
Science, later. Saving, now.
Look out!
Oh, no. No!
Intruder alert.
Spider-Man!
Huh?
Oh, really?
After all I've lived through,
it ends on a steel slab and a laser?
What the what?
Wow! Thanks!
Remarkable.
Doc?
Uh,
high-five?
What'd you do?
I saved you. With science!
Doc, did you just...
I appreciate the hand... Help! Help.
I-I mean help.
But you shouldn't have taken the serum.
Perhaps.
But I feel incredible.
Yeah?
Well, my spidey-sense
just started ringing like
a firehouse and I'm guessing
you're the alarm.
Well, it can't be me. I'm fine.
Look.
Look out!
He brought friends!
We can handle this, Spidey. You and me.
Together.
While impromptu team-ups
are a norm in this biz,
I can honestly say I did not expect...
Spider-Man and Man-Lizard.
Combating evil with
the forces of nature on their side.
Spider-Man and Man-Lizard!
We make a good team, huh?
Team?
Doc, are you feeling all right?
You look a little green.
Doc Ock puts the "mad" in mad scientist.
Who knows what his lizard juice
is doing to you.
I'm great.
I do have a slight itch
at the back of my brain,
but maybe more.
Hey, Doc! A little help here!
With some fine tuning,
Otto's work could cure me
and thousands like me.
I need to ask him
if he has more of this substance
hidden somewhere.
Imagine what other advances
the world might have
if we could hold him back from
the brink of his madness.
Other advances?
I don't think you're in the win
column yet.
I get that you and
Ock were friends back in college,
but the only mind that could even begin
to make sense of Ock's
weird work is Ock's!
Exactly. But not if we don't
give him the chance!
Doc?
Oh, boy.
No.
What happened to you?
If Otto is the only one who can
perfect my change,
then I must find him.
Whoa!
His great power...
Now my responsibility.
Stop! Wait up!
You need a Jurassic intervention!
Oh, don't lizards have ears?
Whatever's happening to you needs
to be looked at, fast.
Uh, besides, finding Ock is a needle
in a haystack.
It's impossible.
No,
I can smell him,
like lizards do.
With my tongue. He's in the sewers.
Ew.
That is gross on every level.
You need real help,
before you start spending
all day eating flies
and looking for hot rocks to lie on.
Spider-Man to SHIELD: Need backup.
I can reach Otto.
SHIELD will just lock him up,
take all this from me.
I can't lose him again.
May be too late for that,
but it's not too late to tail you.
Tail. I slay myself.
Web brain, where you at?
Sam! I'm... Is that limbo music?
Oh, May pulled it out. It's killer!
No. "Killer" is a lizardy Doc Connors
on his way to find Doc Ock.
Meet me in the sewers at these...
Sewers?
Hmm. Sounds like a dream come poo.
I-I mean "true." No, I mean "poo."
Trace my coordinates. Get here!
You got it, big guy.
And we'll bring the air freshener.
What do you want me to say?
"You're welcome"?
You took an untested formula
that wasn't even yours!
You deserve what you got.
Don't mock me, Otto.
Perfect this and it help millions.
You laugh at me? Your savior-er?
Can you hear yourself, freak?
You've taken the mind of a genius
and turned it into a pea-brain.
I'm just as smart as I ever were!
Was. Ever was-er.
I know how to fix you.
But I do like what the serum
has done with your skin,
monster.
You want monster, Octopus?
I'll show monster!
I need options.
Plan one:
Let them rip each other to shreds.
Plan two: Call the team again.
No signal here in Smellville.
Plan three:
Outmatched and alone,
like in the action movies.
Three it is.
And here I am without my popcorn.
Spider-Man, protect me.
Spidey,
can you hear me?
Web-head, are you there?
Web-head, do you copy? Hello?
Dr. Connors, please! Don't do this!
Oh!
See?
I knew there was still a good guy
inside that lizard skin.
Stay out of my way!
We have to stop meeting like this.
This is no time for your puerile
attempts at humor!
Puerile?
I don't know what that means,
but when I find out...
Hey!
You are not going to hurt my friend!
You said you could fix him!
There's no "him" to fix.
It's one hundred percent reptile now.
He's not an "it"!
Your serum is making him irrational.
It could've happened to any of us.
Stop!
Connors! No!
I'm not giving up on you!
I know you're still in there.
And Ock knows how to get you out,
but you have to help me help you!
Say "cheese" for flash-webs!
Sorry to use your own tech against you,
Doc.
Neither one of us will escape here alive,
unless...
Please don't say it.
We team up.
Spider-Man, super-villain team-up.
My brain goes to some strange
places sometimes.
This way. I have a plan.
You ever feel like the title "Doctor"
might be slightly undeserved in your case?
It worked, didn't it?
Yeah, you make a solid dog-catcher.
What did you put in that serum, Ock?
Whoa, whoa!
Okay, Ock, plan B?
Have you ever heard
the term "sacrificial lamb"?
Spidey sense!
Hey!
No one rang the recess bell!
Come back here! Tell me the cure!
Why don't you just go steal it from
my lab where he stole my serum.
Come on! You know me!
Me, Spider-Man. You, Doc Connors!
Ooh! My bad on the snout kick,
but I got to run!
Hey, why don't you follow me?
This way.
Come on! Come on, I dare you!
Hunt? Yes!
Hunt, no.
Plan? Yes.
Hey! I'm walking here.
Sheesh! Superheroes these days.
No respect for their elders.
This was you plan?
No, this was me plan.
You called, Spidey?
Doc's a lizard? Huh. Cold-blooded.
Already did that one and better.
Y'all play nice, now.
He's still our friend underneath
all that scaly scary.
Back in a few!
Please let this work.
Now,
let's hope my science skills
are up to the task
my fists haven't been able to solve.
Keep him distracted!
Trying.
But he's getting stronger!
You have about two seconds, Spider!
Make it count!
Huh?
Doc Connors, are you okay?
Yeah.
Where am I?
What-What am I doing?
Oh, dude! You turned into a big, ugly...
You were trying to help me.
Things just got a little out of hand.
Ooh, sorry.
Wrong turn of phrase.
No.
No. It's...
Dr. Connors is lucky you found him,
Spider-Man.
We have to help him, Coulson.
He's our responsibility.
He's part of our big, crazy SHIELD family.
Uh-oh.
We got to skedaddle!
Let me know how he is, okay?
Don't worry.
You did your part, we'll do ours.
Dinner!
At the end of a day like today,
a lot of things can come into focus.
Like, solitude's not
all it's cracked up to be.
And my team?
I should get as much time
with them as I can.
Stick together,
like a family.
Oh, Peter, you're just in time!
Sam made dinner.
Sam? Cooks?
He's quite talented.
A bird, some heat. No biggie.
Oh, don't worry, Danny.
I made some grilled tofu for you.
Just like a real family.
My totally amazing family.